couplescompany.com 2014-02-09

# Privacy Policy

** Legal Disclaimer:  **

The articles, opinions and views provided on Couples Company are not intended as medical, legal or financial advice.  All information is provided for **entertainment purposes only**. Features are authored by licensed psychologists, mental health professionals, legal, financial and other experts or by journalists.  Additional content is provided by affiliated companies and Couples Company patrons.  Articles and content contained herein are not to be used as a substitute for medical attention, diagnosis, treatment, or other professional mental health or medical services. As laws, details and personal situations vary from person to person and state to state, articles and content contained  herein are not and cannot to be used as a substitute for legal, parental. health, mental health, career or financial advice. 

**Couples Company   Privacy Policy**

Privacy is as important to us as it is to you. Our founder is a staunch adversary (and really, really, really detests) unsolicited e-mail, direct mail and intrusive telemarketing, which is one of the reasons why at  The Couples Company & via CouplesCompany.com we are commitment to protecting your privacy. We will never sell, rent, publish or distribute your name, email address or other identifiable information collected via the Couples Club registration, during an e-commerce transaction, Web site features or CC cookies to any third party without your consent. In the event that we are sold or acquired by a 3rd party, all members with current contact information will be given the opportunity to remove their information from our systems prior to the transfer or merging of assets.     [TOP](http://www.couplescompany.com/Company/Company/Privacy_policy.htm#top)

**Please Note:**

The Couples Club, its registration procedures and privileges referred to in this document will not be available until we've complete the Beta Testing of our site.

**Information Collection and Use**

CouplesCompany.com is a company about relationships, founded upon marketing principle that dictates putting our customers and their needs first. In order to do this we created the Couples Club, our free membership club, which entitles members to benefits, discounts and access to our free online classes. Questions asked are purely for the internal marketing, editorial creation and product planning use of CouplesCompany.com. Though detailed, this information allows us to decided what products to carry, what price ranges will suit our membership, where to look for special offers for our members, plus the direction of our editorial, courses and other service offerings. For auditing purposes, it substantiates our membership and visitor numbers. It also allows us to prevent children from accessing content not suited to their age. Any personal information collected on CouplesCompany.com is knowingly and voluntarily provided by customers and visitors to our site. Under no circumstance is this information ever sold, leased, published or rented to a third party without your expressed consent. Should changes be made to our privacy policy, all club members in our database will be notified of the changes and given the opportunity to opt-out of their membership   [TOP](http://www.couplescompany.com/Company/Company/Privacy_policy.htm#top)

**Mergers, Acquisitions or Sale**

In the event that Couples Company is bought, merged or acquired by a third party, all members of the Couples Club with valid contact information will be notified prior to the third party taking possession of Couples Company.  This notification will ask whether Sensualist's Club members prefer to remain members after the transfer or prefer to remove their information from the Couples Club prior to the transfer.  Federal law and tax requirements mandate we keep on file records relating to purchases for up to seven years.  This includes online transactions initiated via Couples Company.  Information contained in these documents can not be changed or eliminated in the event of a sale or transfer.  However information collected for commerce purposes will never be used to contact a customer unless it relates to the transaction covered within the context of the document.  This requirement will be a non-negotiable item in the event of a sale, acquisition or merger of Couples Company with a third party. [TOP](http://www.couplescompany.com/Company/Company/Privacy_policy.htm#top)

**Third Party Collection of information on  
 CouplesCompany.com:**

Many of our shopping functions are outsourced. Should you choose to purchase from a CouplesCompany.com vendor, you will be prompted for information and given the opportunity to submit to that vendor individually or allow CouplesCompany.com to drop in your name, shipping address, and phone number from your Couples Club member file. 

Your address and phone number are required to ship products. Your email address will be used to send you two emails following a purchase, one to confirm your order has shipped, and the second to provide an itemized order summary with your order number and tracking number so that you can find the status of your order. If necessary, a CouplesCompany.com customer service representative may contact you by telephone to resolve any issues concerning your order.

We may occasionally run contests and other similar promotions on our site. These contests are open to Couples Club Members only and do not require any additional personal information to enter. As a member, you are automatically eligible unless your state or country laws exempt you. Winners of cash prizes and merchandise will be required to complete all personal income forms required by their government to claim prizes. Winners of publishing contracts will be required to sign appropriate publishing contracts.   [TOP](http://www.couplescompany.com/Company/Company/Privacy_policy.htm#top)

Other areas within CouplesCompany.com where we use  
 your information:

**1.** IP address –

  1. Diagnose problems with our server and Web site  
 administration. 
  2. Used to identify you and your shopping cart. 

**2.** Your name & password 

  1. Verify that you are a registered customer
  2. Prevent anyone else who may have access to your computer  
 from ordering in your name without your express permission. 
  3. Prevents your children from accessing content on  
 CouplesCompany.com not appropriate to their age. [TOP](http://www.couplescompany.com/Company/Company/Privacy_policy.htm#top)

| 

Security measures will be in place upon our launch to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Credit card number and expiration date will be stored on our secure server with your account so that if you choose, you will not have to fill out this information again during future visits and purchases through CouplesCompany.com and CouplesCompany.com vendors. This information is used solely for billing purposes when you order from CouplesCompany.com and is always encrypted and transmitted safely over the Internet using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology.

An additional feature on CouplesCompany.com allows members to email cards, messages and greetings to their partner. These email addresses are neither stored by CouplesCompany.com nor will these individuals be contacted by us. 

CouplesCompany.com may share non-personal, non-individual information in aggregate form with our vendors and marketing partners for research purposes. This includes aggregate data about our customers, sales, traffic patterns, and related site information. You always have the opportunity to opt-out of receiving future mailings from CouplesCompany.com or our partners; see the section below entitled [Opt-out](http://www.couplescompany.com/Company/Company/Privacy_policy.htm#optout). 

CouplesCompany.com has third party relationships with credit card processing companies, shipping companies, vendors and the company from which we lease our servers. These companies only have access to information that is necessary for each to fulfill their respective roles in completing our customers' orders. CouplesCompany.com reserves the right to share personal information with legal authorities to the extent required by law.  [TOP](http://www.couplescompany.com/Company/Company/Privacy_policy.htm#top)

**Co-branded Relationships and Strategic Partners  
**Users may experience CouplesCompany.com within a co-branded environment alongside one of our partners. These companies are strategic partners. Co-branded pages are recognizable by two methods. 1) By the presence of a "frame" either at the top the page and/or when both companies' brand logos are presented together on the page. 2) By a separate browse window opening to allow access to the partners site without leaving Couples Company. In such situations, individual user information may be shared only between our two companies in an effort to better understand and meet our customers' needs. An example of this would be your region of the country or zip code. Should you have additional privacy concerns, please also refer to the privacy policy of our partner from whose site you visited prior to arriving at CouplesCompany.com.   [TOP](http://www.couplescompany.com/Company/Company/Privacy_policy.htm#top)

**Cookies  
**CouplesCompany.com may at a later date choose to use a feature of your Internet browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. CouplesCompany.com creates and then uses these cookie files to track your clicks as you browse the CouplesCompany.com Web site.

Cookies are like your business card and they tell us whether you have visited CouplesCompany.com previously and to help us determine whether you came to us from a particular Internet link or banner advertisement.  They also help us determine which areas are most important to people like you so we can best determine what features, products and services to carry on CouplesCompany.com.

Cookies allow you to save time and frustration by storing the user names and passwords you use on our site and information on past purchases and personal preferences. By doing this, you do not have to re-enter the information. Should you disable the use of cookies on your browser, you will need to re-enter this information whenever you visit our site. CouplesCompany.com will not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer.   [TOP](http://www.couplescompany.com/Company/Company/Privacy_policy.htm#top)

Opt-Out  
CouplesCompany.com provides customers the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us during your Couples Club registration. We give you the following options to change or modify your information in our database and to choose not to receive future communications. Please review our **[Zero Tolerance Spam Policy.](http://www.couplescompany.com/PreLaunchFAQ.htm#SPAM)**   This is as much for our members' benefit as our own. 

**Contacting CouplesCompany.com  
**For Questions, concerns and curiosities about the CouplesCompany.com privacy statement and Web site, please contact us at:

**Couples Company, Inc.  
6250 Canoga Ave #483  
Woodland Hills, CA. 91367**

**(310) 594-3728  
Local & International**

PUBLIC @ CouplesCompany.com
